# JURBE JUBET

NO 20 Low Cost, Pankshin, Plateau State, Nigeria jjubet@gmail.com 2348068940637

## **OBJECTIVE**

I'm looking for full time work in the business industry to contribute to the development of the industry.

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

As an experienced Banker, Working in the banking industry for over 10 years, i have been exposed to various key Practice within the banking industry and am capable of working in any banking/Financial institution. I am always among the highest appraisal ratings within my Managers subordinates in all the departments and banking institutions i have worked in. After eight years within the Nigerian banking system, and 5 years in an International Bank (Standard Chartered Bank) i am currently seeking a new challenge which will utilize my meticulous attention to detail, excellent conduct and vast knowledge in the financial sector.

I recently completed the Retail Banking I (One) certification with the Retail Banking Academy London. An organization internationally recognized in training retail bankers around the world on best retail banking processes and conducts. The Certificate is a 3 stage learning process and awards a final certificate of Certified Retail Banker.

I am currently a PG student of Cyber security in the University of Essex. This is because I have realised how the world has gone digital and want to expand my knowledge in the digital environment. I have so far learnt the following;

- Confidentiality, integrity and availability (CIA).
- Implications of security breaches.
- Identify and mitigate vulnerabilities and threats.

My career goal is to deliver the best in all I have to offer as I believe every opportunity that presents itself to me is as a God given assignment.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

#### **Standard Chartered Bank**

Victoria Island Lagos

## Analyst, Financial Crime and Compliance

This a full time job. Oct 2019 to date

Assess risks arising from products/segments / geographies / customers/ transactions Identify and escalate any potential risks AML/ and other financial crime risks to the relevant stakeholders.

#### Standard Chartered Bank

Kano, Nigeria Feb 2014 - Present

### **Teller Service Manager**

This is a full time job. Feb 2014 to Nov 2018

0

## First City Monument Bank Plc

Yola, Adamawa, Nigeria Jul 2007 - Sep 2012

## Branch Operations

This is a full time Job. I moved from different Departments within the 6 years i was there.

- Customer Service Officer
- Funds Transfer and Clearing Officer
- Cash Officer
- Acting Head of Operations

#### **QUALIFICATIONS**

## Abubakar Tafawa Balewa University Bauchi

Bauchi, Nigeria 1999 - 2005

## Boys Secondary School (BSS) Gindiri

Jos Plateau State, Nigeria 1996

## Bachelor of Technology in Industrial Chemistry

West African Examination Council Certificate

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Analytical Skill
- Microsoft Office
- Customer Service
- Cash Management
- Computer Networking Skill
- Numerical Skill
- Marketing Skill
- Financial Management
- Operational Risk Management Skill
- Data Analysis

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

#### **Interpersonal Relationship**

Ability to relate well with employees and colleagues

#### **Team Work**

Ability to work as a team and be a major team player or team leader

#### Leadership Skill

Ability to set examples and lead

#### **Comunication and Emphaty**

Ability to listen and communicate clearly

#### Willingness to learn

Seeking clarification and learning new ideas. reading to add knowledge

#### Time management

Ability to manage time and prioritise events

#### **Detailed**

Paying attention to details

#### Positive attitude

Very Positive and not easily discouraged.

#### **Critical Thinking**

Versatile in thinking, creativity

#### **Result oriented**

Ability to achieve goals and focus on results

## **COMMUNITY & VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

## **National Youth Service Corps**

Edo State, Nigeria Jan 2006 - Dec 2006



## **NYSC Member**

This is a National service Program

#### **INTERESTS**

- Watching Adventure and Detective movies
- Computer games

- Playing Chess game
- Puzzle Games

#### **REFEREES**

## **Professor Jotham Kangdim**

Principal - School Of Theology Gindiri

jothamkangdim@gmail.com 2348036186118

#### Paul Alimi Bello

Senior Regional Operations Manager - Standard Chartered Bank

PaulAlimi.Bello@sc.com 2347064186550

#### **Professor Usman Shuaibu**

Professor of Chemistry - Federal University Lokoja Nigeria

shuaibuso@yahoo.com 2349097679444